teentoday.co.uk 2003-06-18

# Privacy Policy Statement

**Privacy Statement for teentoday.co.uk**

teentoday.co.uk has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: teentoday.co.uk. 

IP Address

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Cookies

Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies (on our message boards to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site's optional registration forms allow users to give us demographic information (like their post code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

Links

This site contains links to other sites. **teentoday.co.uk** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Contests

We also run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their post code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We do not store your email addrss after you have been added to our mailing list.

Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

Correct/Update

This site gives users the following option for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

email [ editor@teentoday.co.uk](mailto:editor@teentoday.co.uk)

Changes

We may from time to time change our privacy policy. The updated privacy policy will be available from the teentoday.co.uk home page.

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Oliver Meakings @ teentoday.co.uk, 41A Deepcut Bridge Road, Camberley, Surrey, GU16 6QT. Or email [ editor@teentoday.co.uk](mailto:editor@teentoday.co.uk).
